
let mediumGames = {"0":{"question":"000900560000000709000007030020000090000008013897000456312049600064000021908001005","answer":"731984562245136789689257134123465897456798213897312456312549678564873921978621345"},"1":{"question":"000090400000056009069000000000540000406109000000003500020004070740915862905000001","answer":"132798456874256139569431728318542697456179283297863514621384975743915862985627341"},"2":{"question":"000201800023000400008069000010000098007800000609007030730680000840900076005004001","answer":"496231857123578469578469123214356798357892614689147235731685942842913576965724381"},"3":{"question":"870600050000200000560000000010005080000890003000000400301080006680021040900006812","answer":"872613954193254768564978231219345687456897123738162495321489576685721349947536812"},"4":{"question":"000000000030000600000000105000000780000090200000010006300520090508971062902806541","answer":"124365978735189624689247135216453789457698213893712456361524897548971362972836541"},"5":{"question":"000005090000000000009140030000050080407090362000700004030600047700010850908500621","answer":"216375498384269175579148236621453789457891362893726514135682947762914853948537621"},"6":{"question":"900500000000007080007300024000000008300008005708100030430000900000943001800215600","answer":"912584367543627189687391524156432798394768215728159436431876952265943871879215643"},"7":{"question":"004000000023460000007009200000040090340007600079500300400800051000050402852910000","answer":"164725839923468175587139246218346597345297618679581324436872951791653482852914763"},"8":{"question":"506000007004000060000000000000500608000000000698103470000005980860902710972004056","answer":"516249837324781569789356241143597628257468193698123475431675982865932714972814356"},"9":{"question":"000080000004000000070000009012400007007308106680012000003605980000900002960820700","answer":"129586374534197268876234519312469857497358126685712493243675981758941632961823745"},"10":{"question":"900500040003000500050000200200306000300001026600274010506700080040980050092040701","answer":"927568143163427598458139267214356879375891426689274315536712984741983652892645731"},"11":{"question":"000000000004009000000000100003405089050090030708000015005704962002006053000530801","answer":"231647598584129376679358124123475689456891237798263415315784962842916753967532841"},"12":{"question":"000001008000000307700005000300006000400008003008023015521800604800910000074060830","answer":"235671948146289357789345126312456789457198263698723415521837694863914572974562831"},"13":{"question":"060007000103008000070120008010056897006009004800000000000400900000095631085630702","answer":"268947513143568279579123468314256897756389124892714356631472985427895631985631742"},"14":{"question":"902700010030200000000109000010465000000000100000000400320670958000000001897530640","answer":"942753816135286794678149523713465289264897135589312467321674958456928371897531642"},"15":{"question":"700030010100407509000120000015000000006700000097000030000072960001803000072014000","answer":"724935618138467529569128347215349786346781295897256134483572961651893472972614853"},"16":{"question":"080070000000308070000020008000056090006800013008200405530700080040900000962500000","answer":"184675329629348571375129648213456897456897213798213465531764982847932156962581734"},"17":{"question":"000104002000000000000206000000000089000800026608720000530040900800017603076038201","answer":"357194862162385497489276315215463789743859126698721534531642978824917653976538241"},"18":{"question":"054030000000070009000056003000040600000000370000062500021800706643725081970014000","answer":"154239867236178459789456123312547698465981372897362514521893746643725981978614235"},"19":{"question":"600800203000160070080200000000056089050000000008000060302001950800000630001573000","answer":"617845293234169578589237146123456789456798312798312465342681957875924631961573824"},"20":{"question":"002008407040000000000000005020000000000001000090302504230700956060920041074615020","answer":"312568497547139268689247135728456319453891672196372584231784956865923741974615823"},"21":{"question":"030745000004000000060129300000006097000007003700010006001070000005900000972581000","answer":"138745269294368175567129348413256897826497513759813426381674952645932781972581634"},"22":{"question":"098500620120000009400080130010300700000008200000000050007840962000030805000070403","answer":"798513624123467589456289137214356798365798241879124356537841962641932875982675413"},"23":{"question":"010607000004100000000000105023000000050091300800002451345700900760003500901524000","answer":"219657834574138296638249175123475689456891327897362451345786912762913548981524763"},"24":{"question":"000098070000350009000000005200005000400010300690700450300582000862071043900034010","answer":"523198674146357289789246135231465798457819326698723451314582967862971543975634812"},"25":{"question":"000000800000070000700050030010060000000819326000007045000601072860700450900043081","answer":"125934867346278519789156234213465798457819326698327145534681972861792453972543681"},"26":{"question":"000001000034000070700006000213400709050000200000103006301004907600007000970602000","answer":"562371498134289675789546123213465789456798231897123546321854967645937812978612354"},"27":{"question":"000004000004000079007100048300006807456000010009002050600040085800920630040085020","answer":"198274563234568179567139248312456897456897312789312456621743985875921634943685721"},"28":{"question":"001048500000150000080000004000000000400800300798020015300780956005000043947030000","answer":"231648579674159238589372164123965487456817392798423615312784956865291743947536821"},"29":{"question":"000000000040006000079000024100000890000080231008210400002004070837590000964870310","answer":"281459763345726189679138524123645897456987231798213456512364978837591642964872315"},"30":{"question":"870020000004060080500008000100000000400700001708010000000090870040831050000672310","answer":"871325469234967185569148237123456798496783521758219643312594876647831952985672314"},"31":{"question":"000000010000209000700000040200050069406091082097060104020004006060003807000600401","answer":"632547918145289673789136245213458769456791382897362154321874596564913827978625431"},"32":{"question":"006000490100060570070300106002000009457800000008103000020005030800900000065734802","answer":"236517498184269573579348126312456789457892361698173245721685934843921657965734812"},"33":{"question":"060020901020000000000060234004050080056090100000010050600740800000900600005600420","answer":"368524971421379568579168234134256789756893142892417356613742895247985613985631427"},"34":{"question":"000000095000000000070060100210075069056001300807003401305010086062984000900000002","answer":"128347695634159278579268134213475869456891327897623451345712986762984513981536742"},"35":{"question":"090000000000006000468300005004030006350108040000200000000040078000005903070683402","answer":"193452687527896134468317295714539826352168749689274351236941578841725963975683412"},"36":{"question":"006000000020400000070000034210375008050081207000904300430090086000003002802700500","answer":"146537829328419675579268134214375968953681247687924351435192786761853492892746513"},"37":{"question":"000000000020000009508009030004037806300098040700600051001860002002900500090002000","answer":"943786125127453689568219734214537896356198247789624351431865972872941563695372418"},"38":{"question":"604000508103000079000000100010004000000789005798200000030000900000041763907003051","answer":"624197538183452679579368124215634897346789215798215346431576982852941763967823451"},"39":{"question":"900071000100000570000030008004050000006090000780004035400002956670000483000003700","answer":"928571364143268579567439128214356897356897241789124635431782956672915483895643712"},"40":{"question":"300010908000000000709305106000406000005000210000103000520901600030500090900062000","answer":"342617958156289347789345126213456789465798213897123465528931674631574892974862531"},"41":{"question":"300002100106040000709000000000060890000700000000013400002094001001800025970520643","answer":"345972168126348579789156234213465897654789312897213456532694781461837925978521643"},"42":{"question":"000840000030100009000239040120050000006000230800002406312004000005900012007520300","answer":"269845173438167529571239648124356897756498231893712456312674985645983712987521364"},"43":{"question":"000060100020300070007140200000400000400000320098030015040007002000904500005620001","answer":"354762189129358674867149253532471896416895327798236415641587932273914568985623741"},"44":{"question":"759000008003000000060070030000050807000891200000007000530702960042900703900004502","answer":"759136428123548679468279135214653897375891246896427351531782964642915783987364512"},"45":{"question":"010000024000100080000200006000400800000000003897310405000001008000903001061084372","answer":"315698724246137589789245136123456897654879213897312465432761958578923641961584372"},"46":{"question":"002060090130270068000000000000000000400800000708000000300685970007932000986000302","answer":"842163597135279468679458123251346789463897215798521634324685971517932846986714352"},"47":{"question":"000030000204006700008000100000507000000000030000002005301600908602000041985714060","answer":"167238459294156783538479126823597614459861237716342895341625978672983541985714362"},"48":{"question":"000700000000000508009008030000075089465091020008000400006587940007002000902000751","answer":"851734296234169578679258134123475689465891327798326415316587942547912863982643751"},"49":{"question":"002608000130247009000000000200060000047000000000000400020586900750000860086700540","answer":"472698135135247689698135274219364758847951326563872491324586917751429863986713542"},"50":{"question":"000000008120000600000100000010405890000619300000023005001040900845932700960000000","answer":"356294178127358649498167253213475896584619327679823415731546982845932761962781534"},"51":{"question":"090235000030600000000049000003006000000000302009010450300000084017000003904503701","answer":"196235847432678915578149236253486179841957362769312458325791684617824593984563721"},"52":{"question":"007080000123000509000230047004306790350010000700020005430000001602000000891503000","answer":"547189236123467589968235147214356798359718462786924315435692871672841953891573624"},"53":{"question":"006000200000009008000006340003000000057690000000003100001700980802905030904832500","answer":"146358279325479618789126345213587496457691823698243157531764982862915734974832561"},"54":{"question":"000007004200000000000000000103000000008000000079083405315874062700000500986532741","answer":"531267894264398157897451236123945678458726319679183425315874962742619583986532741"},"55":{"question":"000000005020406000008200006000060000000098000000124063630040978040980651900000402","answer":"163879245529436187478251396314765829256398714897124563631542978742983651985617432"},"56":{"question":"000000000003058000609000058200005806356080710008004005001802067000000003907030001","answer":"185967432423158679679423158214375896356289714798614325531842967862791543947536281"},"57":{"question":"950000000130200070000000200013000007460000000000620015001040000047916820090002040","answer":"952187364134269578786435291213594687465871932879623415621348759547916823398752146"},"58":{"question":"000100300000060000000380100010600000065790010098241563030006000640000875907402000","answer":"856124397173569248429387156214635789365798412798241563531876924642913875987452631"},"59":{"question":"856009020120050000000068100004000090000801000000620000501700060000080000082506740","answer":"856139427123457689479268135214375896365891274798624351531742968647983512982516743"},"60":{"question":"030697004006100009000040006000056008400000000690000005000060000860070010004821053","answer":"132697584546138279789245136213456798457982361698713425321569847865374912974821653"},"61":{"question":"609000010000050079400060230004005000000091704800000000530706082742900060900000347","answer":"629378415318254679457169238174625893263891754895437126531746982742983561986512347"},"62":{"question":"000000400200007580700050020023009008400600300090300200010000957000005600960023004","answer":"531298476246137589789456123123549768457682391698371245312864957874915632965723814"},"63":{"question":"009020008020000009000400020010005000050000004000040306030050982002910740005084600","answer":"149326578328571469576498123614835297253769814987142356431657982862913745795284631"},"64":{"question":"009062000000000080006000107004030000060090040000204056008001902042000815901020003","answer":"189762534427153689536489127714635298265897341893214756658341972342976815971528463"},"65":{"question":"010000060040009570000250000023060000050000000008710040001624807860001400904583600","answer":"315847962246139578789256134123465789457398216698712345531624897862971453974583621"},"66":{"question":"500000300000250700000130000000000000450000020700002050005074908861020004000501632","answer":"512467389348259761697138245126745893453896127789312456235674918861923574974581632"},"67":{"question":"005049000000057600009000000003000000050008213890003006531002904048900030970000061","answer":"165849327324157689789326145213465798456798213897213456531682974648971532972534861"},"68":{"question":"002000010045008070000039040003050008000090020700000564520003907807920000000080650","answer":"392574816145268379678139245213456798456897123789312564521643987867925431934781652"},"69":{"question":"000000040020009070000100006000006089007001060608020050002604090000000610900578403","answer":"135267948426389571789145236213456789547891362698723154352614897874932615961578423"},"70":{"question":"704000500100500000000000020000306800000800000870000300400600900650982734982030051","answer":"724163598168529473395478126249356817513847269876291345437615982651982734982734651"},"71":{"question":"200100600106000050009050000000000000405300000000000040521734900678900034003065712","answer":"254173689136289457789456123312547896465398271897612345521734968678921534943865712"},"72":{"question":"904000000020000609000000000000046790346708502008002000400020007672000050859670020","answer":"964137285123854679587269134215346798346798512798512346431925867672481953859673421"},"73":{"question":"000000003000000089000000000004000890050891074090024305000700908000983502900046700","answer":"128479653376152489549368127214537896653891274897624315432715968761983542985246731"},"74":{"question":"000500000356170240000000000003000708005007310890010000502000004074900503930005620","answer":"241539867356178249789264135123456798465897312897312456512683974674921583938745621"},"75":{"question":"000170000000000000670000130203000090000791280090023000002006009005902841900500300","answer":"324175968158369472679284135213458697546791283897623514432816759765932841981547326"},"76":{"question":"000390050000006000560008020010000000006080000000600514001030900700905060980760301","answer":"247391658198256437563478129312549786456187293879623514621834975734915862985762341"},"77":{"question":"000000000024000600008100037010000890050091070080000004600004005005912700900530008","answer":"397265481124378659568149237213457896456891372789623514631784925845912763972536148"},"78":{"question":"800000200004008009060000000000000800006800002790002406342071085605023040901504000","answer":"817395264534268719269417538423756891156849372798132456342671985685923147971584623"},"79":{"question":"300070100000006789500180200000000000000718326000000400000000978000007013075001042","answer":"389274165142356789567189234613425897954718326728693451431562978296847513875931642"},"80":{"question":"008004050000000000000000000000000000000091000080603415635012948071040503040538061","answer":"128374659354169287796285134412857396563491872987623415635712948871946523249538761"},"81":{"question":"310205090040060308000000100020056000000790200700000400000600900062904007970002860","answer":"317285694245169378689347125123456789458791236796823451531678942862934517974512863"},"82":{"question":"000600400103000670060000000210000897006000000890014356035040900040900060002036001","answer":"578621439123459678469873125214365897356798214897214356635147982741982563982536741"},"83":{"question":"000070130020450000508100006000005800007298001000010350730000920860020500000507013","answer":"496872135123456789578139246214365897357298461689714352735641928861923574942587613"},"84":{"question":"040000000000000008079008000000075809000001000790024300430087000000900481082046753","answer":"148253697253769148679418235314675829826391574795824316431587962567932481982146753"},"85":{"question":"007020000004000009000000200213400007000000000708000564031500008042931670075084002","answer":"167829453324156789589347216213465897456798321798213564631572948842931675975684132"},"86":{"question":"900003070020007600000000104000300000340790200080005040030502007650004000892670003","answer":"916423578428157639573869124261348795345796281789215346134582967657934812892671453"},"87":{"question":"000001000000450000060230000000300098305008020009024315000800000700003064806972501","answer":"257681943913457682468239157124365798375198426689724315531846279792513864846972531"},"88":{"question":"000300008000008070008000036210030800075800002009020300500607904000900681000140053","answer":"127369548463518279958274136214736895375891462689425317531687924742953681896142753"},"89":{"question":"702000050000050000060000020000000007050009010897000000021094008600807902908602501","answer":"782146359419253786563978124136485297254769813897321465321594678645817932978632541"},"90":{"question":"000004000000000000609007120010060000405700003708100040001876490040930070076502030","answer":"127684359354219768689357124213465987465798213798123546531876492842931675976542831"},"91":{"question":"060870000004050080008009146020065897050000003000000000300007020040900571800021600","answer":"162874359934156782578239146421365897759418263683792415315647928246983571897521634"},"92":{"question":"000500020020409000089000000210350080000800000008004005701005090802000057900782413","answer":"163578924527419368489263571214356789395827146678194235731645892842931657956782413"},"93":{"question":"900870002020050009570120300015307000040090500000061000400002975000000000000700460","answer":"964873152123456789578129346215347698346298517789561234431682975657914823892735461"},"94":{"question":"000962001100000000000000200200070000000080007008614500431000950502091700900503002","answer":"375962481126458379849137265214375896653289147798614523431726958562891734987543612"},"95":{"question":"060000090020000000709000300200000009300090000800000103500040000008900732972683504","answer":"163257498425839671789164325254371869316498257897526143531742986648915732972683514"},"96":{"question":"000680000000007500009000000000000790005798000800000000001060904074901850930074621","answer":"152689347346217589789345162463152798215798436897436215521863974674921853938574621"},"97":{"question":"080007300000008070609020000200040800007200060096000034400792000758610920900800000","answer":"582467319134958672679123458215346897347289165896571234463792581758614923921835746"},"98":{"question":"000062000000000000070100200000400806450080300890600000031000068782000140004831002","answer":"145362789328579614679148235217493856456287391893615427531724968782956143964831572"},"99":{"question":"005009002020008609780006000000000000000800063096023401041007920560010000078002504","answer":"615379842423158679789246135137465298254891763896723451341587926562914387978632514"},"100":{"question":"940000000000000089060200100200005800006008000089024305005712900601980024000006031","answer":"947831652123567489568249173214375896356198247789624315435712968671983524892456731"},"101":{"question":"090024060100060009070009000000070000456801000789030405030047000840000000962580040","answer":"395124867124768359678359124213475698456891273789236415531647982847912536962583741"},"102":{"question":"008200010000000000009008000000306008000019024896004000000902870082573040900680300","answer":"348265917265197483719438265421356798537819624896724531153942876682573149974681352"},"103":{"question":"000060000020000080000000257204300800350091002000024000605012000040086023000540760","answer":"178265934523479186496138257264357819357891642819624375635712498741986523982543761"},"104":{"question":"000000100000000070700005040213006780000008600098710004000004920002001400904530060","answer":"325647198146389572789125346213456789457298613698713254531864927862971435974532861"},"105":{"question":"040100006000000000500000000000030098306009400807000000030065070075921803082703500","answer":"243178956719256384568394721451637298326589417897412635934865172675921843182743569"},"106":{"question":"000000040000100070000040030000060009007090203008072010300086504700023861986500020","answer":"123657948845139672679248135231465789467891253598372416312786594754923861986514327"},"107":{"question":"608003400200059070009068020103000000050000000000000000040785060060000850985624000","answer":"618273495234159678579468123123546789456897231897312546341785962762931854985624317"},"108":{"question":"000080000000040000709235140003000708050008600098702050000870000865020430004563000","answer":"142689573536147289789235146213456798457398612698712354321874965865921437974563821"},"109":{"question":"000025308000160409000000100000050007056709000000013500048000050500892704970000001","answer":"417925368835167429629348175293456817156789243784213596348671952561892734972534681"},"110":{"question":"000037000000059000409000030014000060350091000690800051030540086065913042000006000","answer":"526137498183459627479268135214375869358691274697824351731542986865913742942786513"},"111":{"question":"006000010000000000000109000204000090300800460600000135430602057702010600865900301","answer":"926475813143268579578139246214356798357891462689724135431682957792513684865947321"},"112":{"question":"000060500040230600008100000012000090006008102007600305020000960003926000900001703","answer":"239864517145237689678159234312475896456398172897612345521743968783926451964581723"},"113":{"question":"006000010000000000000034260300000807050390100080712340701000000800020630900500002","answer":"236859714194276583578134269312465897457398126689712345721643958845927631963581472"},"114":{"question":"070000806004600050000000030003060700400008000098000065320506908045912003000800500","answer":"172395846934681257586274139253469781461758392798123465327546918845912673619837524"},"115":{"question":"008000000000000000060000120200506789056000201800003600631702900000900000982000017","answer":"128367495345291876769485123213546789456879231897123654631752948574918362982634517"},"116":{"question":"000640000030000609060000000020460090400090300089010456310820000600070020072500041","answer":"297643185534281679861957234123465798456798312789312456315824967648179523972536841"},"117":{"question":"400005006000000479078000000003450708506800003890123000350000980000900300000501000","answer":"412795836635218479978364125123456798546879213897123564351642987264987351789531642"},"118":{"question":"938040000020000000007000020000450000050700200000003000000604000040875930075931640","answer":"938142567124567389567389124213456798456798213789213456391624875642875931875931642"},"119":{"question":"000080306000060480000040025000050790500000000097203564001804900780935000050000000","answer":"124589376375162489968347125213456798546798213897213564631824957782935641459671832"},"120":{"question":"860190034003400000000038060000006090300000420008004005000000802000000953900573641","answer":"865197234273465189149238567421356798357819426698724315536941872714682953982573641"},"121":{"question":"000090000000208079000007000200006700456780003790003560000604007000002650067800030","answer":"172395846345268179689417325213546798456789213798123564521634987834972651967851432"},"122":{"question":"000000001000000009009000034200405097000879003890010050030000900000980340000530602","answer":"324697581158243769679158234213465897546879123897312456435726918762981345981534672"},"123":{"question":"000900010000300080000008030003465097050709003090000060041027900000000042902030070","answer":"238946715415372689679158234123465897856719423794283561341627958567891342982534176"},"124":{"question":"000000000000000080500209100020006008007090301000371040041680972060903800800724003","answer":"619538427234167589578249136123456798457892361986371245341685972762913854895724613"},"125":{"question":"000005000230078000060000070100050000000700000897000045302047006648920700070061320","answer":"781295463234678519569134278123456897456789132897312645312547986648923751975861324"},"126":{"question":"050000003000000578089200100003406000040000200090710000302584690860000000974000000","answer":"451678923236149578789235146123456789547893261698712435312584697865927314974361852"},"127":{"question":"080000034003000080000008000210007008300000240000620000508040001600900000970863452","answer":"182576934753294186496318725219437568365189247847625319538742691624951873971863452"},"128":{"question":"060000400100406780008009036004000000005208000096000020001640978000900503000530040","answer":"269873451153426789478159236824365197715298364396714825531642978642987513987531642"},"129":{"question":"801900003000060000600000000020006000000000230098010506010094807007802904984001002","answer":"841925673235167489679348125123456798456789231798213546312594867567832914984671352"},"130":{"question":"000705902103000500000030100000000709357800000090000003031000805005971324040000600","answer":"468715932123469578579238146214356789357892461896147253731624895685971324942583617"},"131":{"question":"004020100023050700007000000000000690040200007000000300401802060600010873070605401","answer":"564728139123459786897163254215347698349286517786591342431872965652914873978635421"},"132":{"question":"560100000000000009000300020010400000007000010000000045020600981806930402940502673","answer":"562149738134728569789356124213465897457893216698217345325674981876931452941582673"},"133":{"question":"040120090003500007500000023000306709350000000008200056400800970800000000000641538","answer":"647123895123589467589467123214356789356798214798214356461835972835972641972641538"},"134":{"question":"000673000004000008670040030000000089050007203090012056340000000000080004082730500","answer":"128673945534129678679548132213456789456897213897312456341265897765981324982734561"},"135":{"question":"680020000020000000000000030000030700057000000806704350500940067041685903000270000","answer":"683127495425369178179458236214536789357892614896714352532941867741685923968273541"},"136":{"question":"000000020000100000600007104123000000400090317000003402310000090500036281900020500","answer":"741359628238164975659287134123475869465892317897613452312548796574936281986721543"},"137":{"question":"000000000120000709060300125010000090306000070000020000500800007007913852902000401","answer":"459271386123568749768394125214637598396185274875429613531842967647913852982756431"},"138":{"question":"000600070040000060600000000302065000050890213007100400520006040000014602964702500","answer":"235641879148279365679358124312465987456897213897123456521936748783514692964782531"},"139":{"question":"200000000130050080009300025300000800400700001090003000501600070083592610900810000","answer":"258476139134259786679381425312945867465728391897163542521634978783592614946817253"},"140":{"question":"070000001003006000080100340200300000000070000000061000401690000800714093907830400","answer":"572483961143926578689157342216348759354279186798561234431695827825714693967832415"},"141":{"question":"007040068000689000000007000003465780006090210708000006001070092000000071002014630","answer":"127543968345689127689127354213465789456798213798231546531876492964352871872914635"},"142":{"question":"000000500105060389609000020003070600050801070700020000000704930804006750060000800","answer":"238149567145267389679538124923475618456891273781623495512784936894316752367952841"},"143":{"question":"300000000000000000080020040003000600406001000008260100532014978800975402000002500","answer":"314586729275349816689127345123458697456791283798263154532614978861975432947832561"},"144":{"question":"000000030000050000000000008200005000050800700780604315531706000670012003900000167","answer":"125487639863259471497163258214375896356891724789624315531746982678912543942538167"},"145":{"question":"090002000000000160078000000000050000450807002700013500002084070807005021060720003","answer":"194362758325978164678541239213456897456897312789213546932184675847635921561729483"},"146":{"question":"809040000000000009000000008000000897000097100798014006001002000000903710907050063","answer":"829345671134678529576129438412536897653897142798214356341762985265983714987451263"},"147":{"question":"000040800040200070089000205000000090400009003700002406501603080007094612964020000","answer":"273945861145268379689137245312456798456789123798312456521673984837594612964821537"},"148":{"question":"310007065000000008000006003000000090000000382007060000501002840602980030970000250","answer":"314827965256139478789456123123548697465791382897263514531672849642985731978314256"},"149":{"question":"200010000000260509060409020000000790000897031000003400001730005000950007970680000","answer":"249315876137268549568479123813546792452897631796123458621734985384951267975682314"},"150":{"question":"900600020003008000000000005000000000007800000000000310031065982092003407086924001","answer":"914657823253418679678239145125346798347891256869572314431765982592183467786924531"},"151":{"question":"400020800000309000000000200010000679040000000000000054050704980862905703904002510","answer":"431526897285379461697481235518243679349657128726198354153764982862915743974832516"},"152":{"question":"036095478000000360009000005012400090000000200607023000001000000004000752973582001","answer":"136295478245178369789346125312457896458619237697823514521764983864931752973582641"},"153":{"question":"000000000000034009000150000010000000000708100897000400500043070678029041000871650","answer":"132987564765234819489156237316492785254768193897315426521643978678529341943871652"},"154":{"question":"500000000000000600070000020004006090306008040800000036001840907740915803080673000","answer":"563127489219384675478569321154236798396758142827491536631842957742915863985673214"},"155":{"question":"000600050000000600509000000004360708300709004000200500030872065080901002000000013","answer":"143698257728153649569427381214365798356789124897214536431872965685931472972546813"},"156":{"question":"000039000100057080570000020000006098000800000800000004020684907740013802000000301","answer":"268139475194257683573468129412376598937845216856921734321684957749513862685792341"},"157":{"question":"060293000020400709009070200000360000000010004806004010000002070000901500002507003","answer":"467293158128456739359178246241365897573819624896724315935682471784931562612547983"},"158":{"question":"000500060030060000500000100023000090056700010809002000082001045610004870047000621","answer":"291538467734169582568247139123856794456793218879412356382671945615924873947385621"},"159":{"question":"206091004000207080009340000002460708400000210000020450500008900008070000903000862","answer":"256891374134257689789346125312465798465789213897123456521638947648972531973514862"},"160":{"question":"500000040100489000400000020000000009307000006098070200731002090845016002060003051","answer":"576321948123489567489567123214635789357298416698174235731852694845916372962743851"},"161":{"question":"005060294020000000079000030000000000000000010008030000301027986560080001907004023","answer":"135768294426359178879142635213475869754896312698231457341527986562983741987614523"},"162":{"question":"709000000000450000008009007204300000000090420800620071000742908007903010002510703","answer":"719238564326457189458169237264371895173895426895624371631742958547983612982516743"},"163":{"question":"405008137100000000000030000004300000300800020069070000531082060702046510000513800","answer":"425698137173254689698137245814325796357869421269471358531782964782946513946513872"},"164":{"question":"000504001000060000060000200200000009406007020090000406320045090080001040940780002","answer":"832574961154269387769138254278456139416397825593812476321645798687921543945783612"},"165":{"question":"007040500100060409059100067000006790300200040600471200530000800000800002000710603","answer":"867943521123567489459128367214356798375289146698471235531692874746835912982714653"},"166":{"question":"001002600240000500000000003000040869057600001690003000000875900000960302900000080","answer":"381752694249316578765498123123547869857629431694183257432875916578961342916234785"},"167":{"question":"010000078000000269700036045000050096056089000007002003000500000004893001900021530","answer":"612945378345178269789236145123457896456389712897612453231564987574893621968721534"},"168":{"question":"000002450103050600056009000200030700000098104070200005002040000607900803081070500","answer":"798362451123457689456189237214536798365798124879214365532841976647925813981673542"},"169":{"question":"040080600000000009000009005003000896456000107709000300321500008597020000000070502","answer":"942785613135246789678139245213457896456398127789612354321564978597823461864971532"},"170":{"question":"000000000050120000009000120000050096060892300007010200512000983678000040000085060","answer":"123548679756129438849367125231754896465892317987613254512476983678931542394285761"},"171":{"question":"050000000100000000470000000010365090060780010800004060501642078700001530900000041","answer":"652137489189426357473958126217365894364789215895214763531642978746891532928573641"},"172":{"question":"005001040106000050000005000300006000007009200600720000000860004803914570974530680","answer":"235671849146298357789345126312456798457189263698723415521867934863914572974532681"},"173":{"question":"900000203000000009608000100210040690300008020709000310030020970502000031097000000","answer":"951467283423185769678392145215743698346918527789256314834521976562879431197634852"},"174":{"question":"000004000103000000070060000010600807050000000089001530030700940600003001807410653","answer":"265174389143598762978362415412635897356987124789241536531726948694853271827419653"},"175":{"question":"001960000000108000080000120020005900006000300790000402000094706050706091007021543","answer":"431962875275148639689357124123475968546289317798613452312594786854736291967821543"},"176":{"question":"000700000000000700067100204010000000306090040708210000000502070805070603072030015","answer":"123745869984326751567189234219654387356897142748213596431562978895471623672938415"},"177":{"question":"070320000003000000000000000010506709000090020800270150000082000740013805908000310","answer":"175328496423169578689457231214536789357891624896274153531682947742913865968745312"},"178":{"question":"010000940200000070000000100000000789057890302096700415040000607702930050000607030","answer":"518276943239148576674359128123465789457891362896723415341582697762934851985617234"},"179":{"question":"040090007030000080000006034023460008450819200600700400000504900000970050005002001","answer":"146398527532147689879256134923465718457819263618723495281534976364971852795682341"},"180":{"question":"000008000040000600600000030000056000450700120098000050503004971870020000960003002","answer":"132648597749235618685197234217356489456789123398412756523864971874921365961573842"},"181":{"question":"000001000000060009680000120000006790000709231008020005021070900045092607900804300","answer":"257931846413268579689457123132546798564789231798123465321675984845392617976814352"},"182":{"question":"000004000020008070500070024203000007050007000009000460371005980005982731002000000","answer":"137254698924168375568379124213496857456837219789521463371645982645982731892713546"},"183":{"question":"002000000000000500000000038003406007406807010008000400029000705041025080070930601","answer":"132568974984173562567249138213456897456897213798312456329681745641725389875934621"},"184":{"question":"000000800030000450000300000003000098007000003698720014021600970005007040904530000","answer":"142956837736182459589374126213465798457819263698723514321648975865297341974531682"},"185":{"question":"400090200000000000000005000000050008040009010000002350302804965865001437004000800","answer":"451397286236148579789265143127453698543689712698712354312874965865921437974536821"},"186":{"question":"000004502200150000000030040000060000000098013700000005012549070845070900067020050","answer":"173684592294157638658932147431265789526798413789413265312549876845376921967821354"},"187":{"question":"050700106000000070000050000210400700405000002000300065001600043000921800070003621","answer":"352784196146239578789156234213465789465897312897312465521678943634921857978543621"},"188":{"question":"010700000000006700000000040020005800050007003090002405342070958060940301900000004","answer":"216784539439156782578239146123465897654897213897312465342671958765948321981523674"},"189":{"question":"000000600034000000000008000123400009400800000000310465002501006560904821901000003","answer":"215743698834196257679258134123465789456879312798312465342581976567934821981627543"},"190":{"question":"700800050020000789400070036000000800070090402000724010000000970000000520982500640","answer":"713869254526143789498275136234651897175398462869724315651432978347986521982517643"},"191":{"question":"945003000123007080008000300000360000000090000000004506030806050060901020890500400","answer":"945183672123657984678429315214365798356798241789214536432876159567941823891532467"},"192":{"question":"000003040200100709079040030100000000000000010008010064302500670005007901900020053","answer":"581973246234156789679248135123465897456789312798312564312594678845637921967821453"},"193":{"question":"401290850230008000780000100100405708540800006000000010300000060000000000900032500","answer":"461293857235178649789546123123465798547819236698327415352781964816954372974632581"},"194":{"question":"060000000030009000700400100300007000050000007890600410000730806043080000908065340","answer":"162378954435219768789456123316547289254891637897623415521734896643982571978165342"},"195":{"question":"016207000200009008509008100100040000007000030090070405040605800000080001980000300","answer":"816237594234159768579468123123546987457891632698372415341625879765983241982714356"},"196":{"question":"000094070000000080479120056210600700050780004000201063000050000042000000905000020","answer":"368594172521367489479128356214635798653789214897241563136852947742916835985473621"},"197":{"question":"000060300000200009600347020300070000050001237008603001501000900007900503000084010","answer":"275169348134258679689347125312475896456891237798623451521736984847912563963584712"},"198":{"question":"000500640004060500500000020100600000006008000700203400300800075605900310000301800","answer":"213587649894162537567439128128645793436798251759213486341826975685974312972351864"},"199":{"question":"300008000050030780709000034000400000065870010090010065501600040000000000970540300","answer":"314758692256934781789126534123465879465879213897213465531682947642397158978541326"},"200":{"question":"040008000020007000000060000000030098300801040800720000031000070000940850985102060","answer":"143598627526317984798264135217436598369851742854729316431685279672943851985172463"},"201":{"question":"000000005020000009400000007000300000065708124897204050031806072000032500000001063","answer":"173429685628157439459683217214365798365798124897214356531846972786932541942571863"},"202":{"question":"000001002000008500050009036010300790000002000000107200000004900080915024000703605","answer":"349561872167238549258479136412356798673892451895147263531624987786915324924783615"},"203":{"question":"850630000004150680000000030000000098000090300008070006300080900045916020980003014","answer":"851639472234157689679248135123465798467892351598371246312584967745916823986723514"},"204":{"question":"806005000004000000079040000000050089057090000000000000040681957760004000901537600","answer":"816275394234169578579348126123456789457893261698712435342681957765924813981537642"},"205":{"question":"005040800100009007000050000003405000406708000000003405341000900070031000960874531","answer":"295147863134689257687352149823415796456798312719263485341526978578931624962874531"},"206":{"question":"400000000000000000000000000010006008300089040698010325701045902862971050000020807","answer":"423157689156398274987462531214536798375289146698714325731845962862971453549623817"},"207":{"question":"060004000000567400050020007000000000075008100080401523031000904740003052802005001","answer":"167834295923567418458129367214356789375298146689471523531682974746913852892745631"},"208":{"question":"009000000020000009070159000200405007006090300090200000351700000002980540080030020","answer":"139624875425378169678159234213465987546897312897213456351742698762981543984536721"},"209":{"question":"000000030030250600009360004203005006050800007708613245005000000800026000960500080","answer":"627148539134259678589367124213475896456892317798613245345781962871926453962534781"},"210":{"question":"012900000000000000009406003020500060450080000090200400230690800000072031900000256","answer":"312957648564138729789426513823549167456781392197263485231695874645872931978314256"},"211":{"question":"900500000130060000500109000200000000000000002089010450320641900640980020090023640","answer":"962574138134268579578139264213456897456897312789312456327641985641985723895723641"},"212":{"question":"090040000140006000008050230003005000056800000009012056500600040030904001900001002","answer":"392748615145236789678159234213465897456897123789312456521673948837924561964581372"},"213":{"question":"050001000100078000000000000200530000005000000090620010531700086008000043902803051","answer":"354291678126378495789456132217534869465189327893627514531742986678915243942863751"},"214":{"question":"961000500200000000008000000100000090450000213000312060000600000640901000007540621","answer":"961237584234895176578164932123456897456789213789312465315628749642971358897543621"},"215":{"question":"000700000000008009000000000123405000000001020789006400204500900001904082097010003","answer":"312749658475168239968253174123475896546891327789326415234587961651934782897612543"},"216":{"question":"000830000000200000600450000210000000006008031097000000021605804504902307078010652","answer":"142836579735291468689457123213549786456728931897163245321675894564982317978314652"},"217":{"question":"702008001000000600000100200003060000000000100897000046001046970500903800078501004","answer":"732658491145297638689134257213465789456789123897312546321846975564973812978521364"},"218":{"question":"005000000030000080000038000000065897406700003700310050501674038040591000060023000","answer":"185246379234957186679138425312465897456789213798312654521674938843591762967823541"},"219":{"question":"850000000123570000400020350000000090000801246090005000030406902040000680080012030","answer":"857364129123579468469128357214637895375891246698245713531486972742953681986712534"},"220":{"question":"078004000100000009006000000004000700300700010780100003030876940600000871897001600","answer":"978214356123567489456389127214635798365798214789142563531876942642953871897421635"},"221":{"question":"000900000000000000579020300000400097050200100000700205300090600760801900905642710","answer":"234968571618375429579124368123456897457289136896713245341597682762831954985642713"},"222":{"question":"207041056040000300600000120012000098400100000000003010520090063073000040000030000","answer":"237841956145269387689357124312475698498126735756983412521794863873612549964538271"},"223":{"question":"000910500000400709400300106200007000000100074000200005002840000800690000906705030","answer":"627918543138456729459372186264537918385169274791284365512843697873691452946725831"},"224":{"question":"000000301000400009070100050000005090056789100000000530000872005062031004087500203","answer":"245697381613458729879123456128345697356789142794216538431872965562931874987564213"},"225":{"question":"000000000003000450400103600000056007005009000790001360531400982000000030906030500","answer":"629584173183672459457193628814356297365729814792841365531467982248915736976238541"},"226":{"question":"070080000000409678009300004000000080000198200698704300030040000000003000040070830","answer":"174286593325419678869357124217635489453198267698724315731842956582963741946571832"},"227":{"question":"006001000000006000009000100014365807300089004000120000500042900042097531000503600","answer":"426951783183276459759438126214365897365789214897124365531642978642897531978513642"},"228":{"question":"000000006023000009000000000004060007300000000780014560031542070800931604005670320","answer":"147359286523486719968127435254863197316795842789214563631542978872931654495678321"},"229":{"question":"000090002000050000009000030000005007050700200706820050000002970805031004042680013","answer":"513496782287153469469278135124365897358719246796824351631542978875931624942687513"},"230":{"question":"000800050006000478000050100120000000005000007897061000500030704600904030904700000","answer":"219847356356129478748356129123478965465293817897561243581632794672984531934715682"},"231":{"question":"080010450000000700000070100010005007060700014708024065530000070072500600940000020","answer":"387216459124953786659478132413685297265739814798124365536842971872591643941367528"},"232":{"question":"040000000130000000000030005000400007007360100008712400500080000063970512070520800","answer":"245697381136845279789231645312458967457369128698712453524183796863974512971526834"},"233":{"question":"000002000000000009000008030210000090460080103007200040500604978006091050080030010","answer":"143962587852173469679458231218345796465789123397216845531624978726891354984537612"},"234":{"question":"090084060004060009000150230010405090000890000780000000000000006840916700067030001","answer":"192384567534267189678159234213475698456891372789623415321748956845916723967532841"},"235":{"question":"700000005023000080080000000215300607000701028890562000000075900000000070008023400","answer":"741289365623154789589637241215348697364791528897562134436875912952416873178923456"},"236":{"question":"600100000103008060089056000010030690000801402800000010001702000002900080970005240","answer":"645129837123478569789356124214537698356891472897264315431782956562943781978615243"},"237":{"question":"000000100003060500000030048010000000000097010609810300000051982052083060001024750","answer":"246578139183469527597132648718346295435297816629815374374651982952783461861924753"},"238":{"question":"000800000020000080508100000210000090057090040009210050030540920840900700000703400","answer":"164832579923475681578169234216354897357698142489217356731546928845921763692783415"},"239":{"question":"060000004120000008000100035200006009307091020096000153030000092040080000900002307","answer":"563278914124359678879164235215436789387591426496827153631745892742983561958612347"},"240":{"question":"008002000005100409070040020100000000006080000807000540350824067700900000080675312","answer":"418392675235167489679548123123456798546789231897213546351824967762931854984675312"},"241":{"question":"000000263000400000689000140200305007050091000000824001035002978800073000000040002","answer":"547189263123456789689237145214365897358791426796824351435612978862973514971548632"},"242":{"question":"070000001120400070680007000204060000006080000098000006531900480840570000907000000","answer":"473652891125498673689137245214369758356781924798245316531926487842573169967814532"},"243":{"question":"000094000230108000080350004023000000050809307090010000341000000000002001060040783","answer":"517294638234168579689357124123475896456829317798613245341786952875932461962541783"},"244":{"question":"010070000200100000000200008020400097056890003000300400000001006760003520980500730","answer":"518679342234158679679234158123465897456897213897312465345721986761983524982546731"},"245":{"question":"009000000003457000000009040210005098050800000890020000031506000005942003980100064","answer":"149238657623457981578619342214365798357891426896724135431586279765942813982173564"},"246":{"question":"075000004000000080000100005003005800050000300000200056031624008802001040040030620","answer":"175382964324596187698147235213465879456879312987213456731624598862951743549738621"},"247":{"question":"000000810003000000000100034000070000050001020807246000001080790762034581905010002","answer":"249763815513428679678159234124375968356891427897246153431582796762934581985617342"},"248":{"question":"000080206000060080000000000000006000006008025800205003480601052001950874950870601","answer":"139587246245169387678423519523716498796348125814295763487631952361952874952874631"},"249":{"question":"000020000000009078079068100210030080000091000000200305000080057762000030905013000","answer":"148327596326159478579468123217534689653891742894276315431682957762945831985713264"},"250":{"question":"005020090000000070409037250200000709006098000007000503030000007600970010008005600","answer":"175426398823519476469837251284351769356798124917264583531682947642973815798145632"},"251":{"question":"400000950005040070000000000000000789540100063000720000300010897860937001970502300","answer":"426371958135849672789256134213465789547198263698723415352614897864937521971582346"},"252":{"question":"000000001100200070070000058310065800060090120807310460020703000000900000086500000","answer":"245678931138259674679134258312465897564897123897312465921743586453986712786521349"},"253":{"question":"000008000005000000080005000000400008406380020897000405001793000008020073070864510","answer":"124938756735146892689275341213457968456389127897612435561793284948521673372864519"},"254":{"question":"090080000000450080500300004200000000007108006000704300001045962800903001905012073","answer":"194286537326457189578391624213569748457138296689724315731845962862973451945612873"},"255":{"question":"456870000000000678000000045210000000060708000807000056000040000602900507970021403","answer":"456872139123495678789136245215369784364758921897214356531647892642983517978521463"},"256":{"question":"040035000000000000008009105003000708456008010700310006010500900504970800807020054","answer":"241835679935167482678249135123456798456798213789312546312584967564973821897621354"},"257":{"question":"008509000000000080000008060010306790000090000890000310001082070600973850000140000","answer":"128569437356417289479238165214356798763891542895724316531682974642973851987145623"},"258":{"question":"002060007000000009008000000103006700450091006000000400031085070590700860080000350","answer":"312469587645378129978152643123546798457891236869237415231685974594713862786924351"},"259":{"question":"000080000005040700608000005000450090006008000009600004001500900507823001860900502","answer":"124785639935146728678239145782451396416398257359672814241567983597823461863914572"},"260":{"question":"000042000020000000008100000014035090005807100090204005001000907006983500002001003","answer":"139542876527368419648179352714635298265897134893214765351426987476983521982751643"},"261":{"question":"090000000030007000000009005000065000000891000869300450321580070700013800900720513","answer":"192658347538147269647239185213465798475891632869372451321584976756913824984726513"},"262":{"question":"801000000200030608000000035000406700056090000700010000312580007007021803900760001","answer":"831675294245139678679248135123456789456897312798312456312584967567921843984763521"},"263":{"question":"008041000000500000000000000000306097005092600009074320031000086000600500846005002","answer":"658941273213587469794263851482356197375192648169874325531429786927618534846735912"},"264":{"question":"060000902000469070000000040205000000306000000098025000031000007057980401982004653","answer":"164578932523469178879231546215346789346897215798125364431652897657983421982714653"},"265":{"question":"090000000000300000000000030000005006000010007080900400701540060800796513065830742","answer":"193254678246387195578169234312475986459618327687923451731542869824796513965831742"},"266":{"question":"640020000030000000000406000000540080406000000897603000010700006074960032068005014","answer":"641328579235197468789456123123549687456872391897613245312784956574961832968235714"},"267":{"question":"087000000000400000400000000000060000005800000790020000031640070072930410049501632","answer":"187253946923486157456197283214765398365819724798324561531642879672938415849571632"},"268":{"question":"000030060020000000400109030214300000300008000780912000002790041805020000071840000","answer":"597234168123586479468179532214357986359468217786912354632795841845621793971843625"},"269":{"question":"040000203023056000600000000200360000358001020000000351030600070802970014001048002","answer":"547189263123456789689237145214365897358791426796824351435612978862973514971548632"},"270":{"question":"050742000100000000470000050000000089060090020800210360500000690700900830901000502","answer":"653742918128359476479168253214536789365897124897214365532481697746925831981673542"},"271":{"question":"009007050000108079578000123020500800050090030006203504040002005000900000002030001","answer":"169327458234158679578469123321546897457891236896273514643712985715984362982635741"},"272":{"question":"200000000030006780000009000010000007400090000700002400621500900073920045000670310","answer":"246187539139256784587349126312465897468793251795812463621534978873921645954678312"},"273":{"question":"000040297000009000009050000000465700000090000698703400301087052070900603900000801","answer":"513846297264179538789352164132465789457298316698713425341687952875921643926534871"},"274":{"question":"005000001046030070080000030300060009450000000090702300520903067064007003003600452","answer":"235874691146239578789156234312465789457398126698712345521943867864527913973681452"},"275":{"question":"380090150025007000000050000000060000050700300000200000000824976840930021900001800","answer":"384692157125347689679158234213465798456789312798213465531824976847936521962571843"},"276":{"question":"006800000000000600780040135103405008050000010600710054300000000060970000001504803","answer":"236851479514397682789642135193465728457238916628719354342186597865973241971524863"},"277":{"question":"700100050000050000400000006004500008070000405895004207507000000041280003980763500","answer":"723146859168952374459378126214537968376829415895614237537491682641285793982763541"},"278":{"question":"700940516020000000000170000000060000000000100000003065341607950070890340082004071","answer":"738942516124356789569178234213465897456789123897213465341627958675891342982534671"},"279":{"question":"000000302000000008080036005003050009047090000690312400000004026070900004904503781","answer":"165789342732145698489236175213457869547698213698312457351874926876921534924563781"},"280":{"question":"001080290000009070009005000000400000007008600008010040012064957060970000074023801","answer":"431687295256139478789245136123456789547398612698712543312864957865971324974523861"},"281":{"question":"000605000005000609670009040010450000000098000000203000001862900700904560900001830","answer":"129645387345187629678329145213456798456798213897213456531862974782934561964571832"},"282":{"question":"050078103000000000080000000003400000065080012807000405006501978570800000900600031","answer":"652978143134256789789134256213465897465789312897312465326541978571893624948627531"},"283":{"question":"000031000103000079000009100000000000000097001080020000001082960670910400892700003","answer":"729431658143658279568279134917345826256897341384126795431582967675913482892764513"},"284":{"question":"507600000000009600400000005004005009000800100090004000630042000070901462042700003","answer":"517623894328459671469178235184365729253897146796214358631542987875931462942786513"},"285":{"question":"000001000120079400009040000200050089000800213000100000530082000700930051980615300","answer":"345261798128379465679548132213457689457896213896123574531782946762934851984615327"},"286":{"question":"000000020005008600070000148123050000000089200708010400000004080560070030900020700","answer":"841697325235148679679235148123456897456789213798312456317964582562871934984523761"},"287":{"question":"600090010000000089009100007000056790050709020708013000301900000000030900975608030","answer":"632897514147365289589142367213456798456789123798213645321974856864531972975628431"},"288":{"question":"000000030200040070600200045020456807000807312009000406000000080017900063900003720","answer":"145678239293145678678239145321456897456897312789312456532761984817924563964583721"},"289":{"question":"000503001000060508500007040005000080000098025000010003000602010650074002902031600","answer":"467583291123469578589127346215346789346798125798215463834652917651974832972831654"},"290":{"question":"006008000000400008089106000000000080000000064698000050030502806800000007975600410","answer":"246358179153497628789126345324765981517839264698214753431572896862941537975683412"},"291":{"question":"000000000300006709080000020000400078450000000798003500010804960864002001930010802","answer":"271598436345126789689347125123459678456781293798263514512834967864972351937615842"},"292":{"question":"000800000100000008780000240004365089050298060090700350030072806002000000075600400","answer":"543826917129457638786139245214365789357298164698714352431572896862941573975683421"},"293":{"question":"006000800000068470070039050014006000000800010009000300002000940000973582890405601","answer":"136547829925168473478239156214356798763894215589712364352681947641973582897425631"},"294":{"question":"500000100020000008068000009004056007306807204709000050000702905840000700975031000","answer":"593248176127569438468173529214956387356817294789324651631782945842695713975431862"},"295":{"question":"000090000000050000000007000204000900005000247090620350031000090872940000900530782","answer":"123498576687153429459267813214375968365819247798624351531782694872946135946531782"},"296":{"question":"000000000103050600060000000000000080000000042890010065631502000042986513005700006","answer":"478369251123457698569128734254693187316875942897214365631542879742986513985731426"},"297":{"question":"000070054000136009600000120000507096400200017000300000000004978702000431000003560","answer":"138972654245136789679458123321547896456289317897361245513624978762895431984713562"},"298":{"question":"000200007030060009078000000000456008400000200000020000300678952082010000700530841","answer":"149285367235167489678349125921456738457893216863721594314678952582914673796532841"},"299":{"question":"000040005240060070609000020000400000406890000097000051031080040062004893980706000","answer":"173249685248561379659378124325417968416895237897623451531982746762154893984736512"}};

const miniBox1 = document.getElementById('mini-box-1');
miniBox1.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 0) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox2 = document.getElementById('mini-box-2');
miniBox2.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 1) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox3 = document.getElementById('mini-box-3');
miniBox3.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 2) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox4 = document.getElementById('mini-box-4');
miniBox4.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 3) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox5 = document.getElementById('mini-box-5');
miniBox5.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 4) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox6 = document.getElementById('mini-box-6');
miniBox6.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 5) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox7 = document.getElementById('mini-box-7');
miniBox7.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 6) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox8 = document.getElementById('mini-box-8');
miniBox8.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 7) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox9 = document.getElementById('mini-box-9');
miniBox9.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 8) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });

const allBoxes = [miniBox1, miniBox2, miniBox3, miniBox4, miniBox5, miniBox6, miniBox7, miniBox8, miniBox9];
const allLines = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('line'));

const minimizeVars = ['box1DecreaseSize', 'box2DecreaseSize', 'box3DecreaseSize', 'box4DecreaseSize', 'box5DecreaseSize', 'box6DecreaseSize', 'box7DecreaseSize', 'box8DecreaseSize', 'box9DecreaseSize'];
const maximizeVars = ['box1IncreaseSize', 'box2IncreaseSize', 'box3IncreaseSize', 'box4IncreaseSize', 'box5IncreaseSize', 'box6IncreaseSize', 'box7IncreaseSize', 'box8IncreaseSize', 'box9IncreaseSize'];
let isMaximizedBool = false;

// number of the box thats maximized
let miniBoxOnNumber;

// all maximizable boxes
const allTapBoxes = getReadingOrientationNumbers();

// the game number (0-299)
let GAME_NUMBER = 0;

// the game state
let GAME_STATE = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];

// the original state of board without touching it
let GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];

// the menu button orientation boolean
let isMenuOpen = false;

// gets all 81 boxes in box order and returns them in reading left to right order
function getReadingOrientationNumbers() {
    let temp = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('tap-box'));
    let ret = [];

    let one = 0;
    let two = 9;
    let three = 18;
    for (let i = 0; i < 3; i++) {
        for (let j = 0; j < 3; j++) {
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(one, one + 3));
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(two, two + 3));
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(three, three + 3));
            one = one + 3;
            two = two + 3;
            three = three + 3;
        }
        one = one + 18;
        two = two + 18;
        three = three + 18;
    }
    return ret;
}

// Maximizes first box, and hides rest. 
async function miniBoxMaximize(num) {
    isMaximizedBool = true;
    document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    // turn off onclick for menu button
    allBoxes[num].style.animation = `${maximizeVars[num]} 0.3s ease-out forwards`;
    miniBoxOnNumber = num;
    hideRest(allBoxes[num]);
}

// if there is a box enlarged, it will minimize it
function minimizeMiniBox() {
    if (isMaximizedBool) {
        allBoxes[miniBoxOnNumber].style.animation = `${minimizeVars[miniBoxOnNumber]} 0.3s ease-out forwards`;
        unHideRest(allBoxes[miniBoxOnNumber]);
        isMaximizedBool = false;
        // turn on onclick for menu button

        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim 3s infinite ease-in-out';
    }
}

// Given a box, hides rest except given box
function hideRest(miniBox) {
    for (let i = 0; i < allBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (!allBoxes[i].isEqualNode(miniBox)) {
            allBoxes[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        }
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < allLines.length; i++) {
        allLines[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    }
}

// Given a box, shows rest except given box since given box has its own animation going on
async function unHideRest(miniBox) {
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
    for (let i = 0; i < allBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (!allBoxes[i].isEqualNode(miniBox)) {
            allBoxes[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        }
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < allLines.length; i++) {
        allLines[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    }
}

// this is for the individual 81 numbers!!
async function clickedTapBox(boxNumber) {
    if (isMaximizedBool && GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[boxNumber] === '0') {  // This ensures that the tap-box number isnt increased by 1 unless the box is maximized
        let theNumber = allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML;
        if (theNumber === '') {
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = 1;
            //GAME_STATE[boxNumber] = '1';
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, '1');
            localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', GAME_STATE);
        } else {
            theNumber = parseInt(theNumber);
            if (theNumber === 9) {
                theNumber = '';
            } else {
                theNumber = theNumber + 1;
            }
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.1s ease-out forwards';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 100));
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = theNumber;
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
            // save game state
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, theNumber.toString());
            localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', GAME_STATE);
        }
    }
    if (isSolved()) {
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
        minimizeMiniBox();
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 1000));
        skipClicked(1);
    }
}

function isSolved() {
    if (GAME_STATE === mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer']) {
        return true;
    } else {
        return false;
    }
}

// personal replace function
String.prototype.replaceAt = function(index, replacement) {
    return this.substr(0, index) + replacement + this.substr(index + replacement.length);
}

// this will start the game either from where left off or new game
function fillStartingState() {
    for (let i = 0; i < allTapBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] !== '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i];
            allTapBoxes[i].style.color = '#545454';
            allTapBoxes[i].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
        } else if (GAME_STATE[i] !== '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_STATE[i];
            allTapBoxes[i].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
        } else  {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = '';
        }
    }
}

// this needs to happen before the function call below
if (!localStorage.getItem("mediumGameNumber")) {
    localStorage.setItem("mediumGameNumber", "0");
    localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', mediumGames[0]['question']);
} else {
    GAME_NUMBER = localStorage.getItem('mediumGameNumber');
    GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    GAME_STATE = localStorage.getItem('mediumGameState');
}
setTimeout(fillStartingState, 2700);

async function menuButtonClicked() {
    if (!isMaximizedBool) {
        if (!isMenuOpen) {
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowToMenuDirection 0.25s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('menu-tray').style.animation = 'menuOpen 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.visibility = 'hidden';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 250));
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim1 3s infinite ease-in-out';
            isMenuOpen = !isMenuOpen;
        } else {
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowToGameDirection 0.25s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('menu-tray').style.animation = 'menuClose 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.visibility = 'visible';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 250));
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim 3s infinite ease-in-out'; 
            isMenuOpen = !isMenuOpen;
        }
    }
}

// SKIP CURRENT GAME
async function skipClicked(num) {
    if (num === 0) {
        menuButtonClicked();        
    }
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 400));
    GAME_NUMBER = parseInt(GAME_NUMBER);
    if (GAME_NUMBER === 299) {
        GAME_NUMBER = 0;
    } else {
        GAME_NUMBER = GAME_NUMBER + 1;
    }
    GAME_NUMBER = GAME_NUMBER.toString();
    GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    GAME_STATE = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    localStorage.setItem("mediumGameNumber", GAME_NUMBER);
    localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', GAME_STATE);
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.3s forwards ease-in-out';

    // clean up the board
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE.length; i++) {
        allTapBoxes[i].style.color = '#f2ebd3';
        allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = '';
    }

    const miniLinesVertical = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('mini-board-vertical-line'));
    const miniLinesHorizontal = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('mini-board-horizontal-line'));
    const linesVertical = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('board-vertical-line'));
    const linesHorizontal = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('board-horizontal-line'));
    for (let i = 0; i < miniLinesVertical.length; i++) {
        miniLinesVertical[i].style.animation = 'none';
        miniLinesHorizontal[i].style.animation = 'none';
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < linesVertical.length; i++) {
        linesVertical[i].style.animation = 'none';
        linesHorizontal[i].style.animation = 'none';
    }
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
    for (let i = 0; i < miniLinesVertical.length; i++) {
        miniLinesVertical[i].style.animation = '';
        miniLinesHorizontal[i].style.animation = '';
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < linesVertical.length; i++) {
        linesVertical[i].style.animation = '';
        linesHorizontal[i].style.animation = '';
    }
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.2s forwards ease-in-out';
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 2700));
    fillStartingState();
}


// Clears the user input from the board
async function clearInputClicked() {
    menuButtonClicked();
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 400));
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.3s forwards ease-in-out';
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 300));
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] === '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = '';
        } else {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i];
        }
        GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(i, GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i]); // update the game state
    }
    localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', GAME_STATE); // update the locally stored variable
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.3s forwards ease-in-out';
}

async function hintClicked() {
    let emptyPos = [];
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_STATE[i] === '0') {
            emptyPos.push(i);
        }
    }
    if (emptyPos.length > 0) {
        menuButtonClicked();
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 400));
        let randomHintIndex = randomInteger(0, emptyPos.length);
        
        let boxNumber = emptyPos[randomHintIndex];

        let theNumber = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer'][boxNumber];
        allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = theNumber;
        allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
        GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, theNumber.toString());
        localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', GAME_STATE);

        if (isSolved()) {
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
            minimizeMiniBox();
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 1000));
            skipClicked(1);
        }
    }
}

function randomInteger(min, max) {
    return Math.floor(Math.random() * (max - min)) + min;
  }

  

// THIS FUNCTION IS FOR TESTING PURPOSES ONLY AND SHALL BE REMOVED IN PROD
async function quickSolve() {
    let one = 0;
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_STATE[i] === '0' && one === 0) {
            one = 1;
        } else if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] === '0') {
            let theNumber = mediumGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer'][i];
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = theNumber;
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(i, theNumber.toString());
            localStorage.setItem('mediumGameState', GAME_STATE);
        }
    }
}